elca-services.ch 2004-12-04

# ELCA: Technology-Consulting-Innovation>> Privacy Policy: job opportunities: careers: Informatiker: software engineer: Programmierer: jobs: software design: business strategy: crm: web design: data warehouse: edm

We collect personal data such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone/fax numbers etc., when voluntarily submitted by visitors. These data are used for the purpose stated at the location where you provide it, i.e., in order to receive press releases, management reports or other financial information or processing an application for employment. By submitting this information, you consent to such use. 

We will not use personally identifiable information for direct marketing or unsolicited follow-up unless you have given us your permission for such use. 

We will use your personally identifiable information only for internal purposes within ELCA, which may include its communication to our affiliates, but also to our third party agents and business partners who have agreed to keep it confidential.

By submitting your data to this website, you expressly agree to its possible transborder transmission. 

**Accessing, deleting or correcting information**  
You may have your personal data deleted, corrected or revised by sending us an [e-mail](mailto:webmaster@elca.ch) via this site or by sending us a letter to: Webmaster, ELCA Holding S.A., avenue de la Harpe 22-24, 1000 Lausanne 13, Switzerland.

You may have access to your data at any time by sending us an [e-mail](mailto:webmaster@elca.ch) , or by writing to us at the address above.

**Security of information**  
Personally identifiable data are kept secure. Only authorized ELCA staff or our business partners or agents (who have agreed to keep the data secure) have access to personally identifiable data.

**General**  
Children and young people under the age of 18 are advised to get permission from a parent or guardian before submitting personally identifiable data to ELCA websites.

Links from this site may take you to sites not covered by this Privacy Policy and we advise you to check the applicable privacy practices yourself. ELCA has no responsibility or liability for these practices.

If you need any more information. please contact us.  
This policy may be modified from time to time.

ELCA HOLDING S.A.  
Ave de La Harpe 22-24  
1000 Lausanne 13  
SWITZERLAND
